tickcounter.com 2018-05-26

# Privacy Policy

This document explains how we collect, use and share data about our users. If you require any more information or have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [tickcounter@tickcounter.com](mailto:tickcounter@tickcounter.com). 

## Collected data

  * Email address
  * Your billing address, first and last name, four last digits and expiry date of your credit card
  * Cookies
  * Automatically Collected Data such as your IP address, connection information such as browser type and version, information about your device including device-type and device identifier, operating system and platform, mobile network data, a unique reference number linked to the data you enter on our system, login details, the site from which you arrived at our service, details of your activity with date and time stamps. 

## Legal basis

We collect data about you because it's necessary for our contract in order to provide you with our service and because we use them to manage and improve our service. Among others, we use your data to send you invoices, process payments or create anonymized traffic analysis. 

## Cookies

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. You can configure your browser to prevent these cookies from being stored, however this may downgrade or break certain elements of TickCounter functionality. For more general information on cookies see [ this Wikipedia article](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie). 

By continuing to use our website, we assume that you consent to use of the following cookies:

### Session, cookie-consent and CSRF-protection

  * **Purpose:** Remebering your account so you don't have to log in every time you navigate to a different page of TickCounter, protection against CSRF attacks, remembering your cookie consent 
  * **Collected data:** Cookies, Automatically Collected Data, email address

### Google Analytics

  * **Purpose:** Anonymized traffic analysis, improving our service
  * **Collected data:** Cookies, Automatically Collected Data and others as specified in their Privacy Policy

### Google AdSense

  * **Purpose:** Displaying ads
  * **Collected data:** Cookies, Automatically Collected Data and others as specified in their Privacy Policy

### Facebook

  * **Purpose:** Providing comment system for TickCounter
  * **Collected data:** Cookies, Automatically Collected Data and others as specified in their Privacy Policy

### Braintree (PayPal)

  * **Purpose:** Processing payments
  * **Collected data:** Cookies, Automatically Collected Data, billing address, first and last name, credit card information and others as specified in their Privacy Policy 

## Data retention

Your data is kept for the time necessary to provide you our service and to comply with legal requirements. You can always send us a request to remove your personal data. 

## Sharing your data

We may share your personal information with companies that supply us with a service:

  * **PythonAnywhere LLP** (our hosting provider)
  * **ZOHO** (our email provider)
  * **Braintree (PayPal)** (processes payments)
  * **Facebook** (provides comment system)
  * **Google** (provides anonymized traffic analysis and delivers ads)

These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

Although our business is based in Poland, your personal data may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area. These transfers will be protected by appropriate safeguards. 

## Changes to this document

We recommend to check this page often as our Privacy Policy may change at any time. If you object to any new changes, please stop using TickCounter and contact us to remove all your data from our servers. 

We use cookies to analyse our traffic, display ads and provide social features.  
Learn more or close this.
